Guide to the Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials, 1940-2011 and undated RL.11802
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Product Testing and Reviews, 1941-2011; undated; 5
  - Household Goods, Toys, etc., 1973-2011; undated; 20
    - Play Pen Playskool, 1984 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0606)
    - Plush Carpets - Blenders, Undated (Box 18, Film-reel RL11802-F16-083)
    - Poultry Bowling, 1993 (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0474)
    - R-4 Packaging Net at Issue, Undated (Box 17, Film-reel RL11802-F16-072)
    - Reel 3 Exercise Machines, Undated (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-123)
    - Rotary Power Mowers - Low Fat Cottage Cheese, Undated (Box 18, Film-reel RL11802-F16-102)
    - Sailboats, Imported Compact Cars, Window Fans, Breakfast Cereals, Slide Projectors, Barbie's Townhouse, Undated (Box 38, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-049)
    - Sailboats, Imported Compact Cars, Window Fans, Breakfast Cereals, Slide Projectors, Barbie's Townhouse, Undated (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-204)
    - Sardine Can Opening, Vitamin C Pills, 3 room Presences, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-018)
    - Screw Drivers, 1975 Jan. 13 (Box 70, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-159)
    - Segment on Air Purifiers, 2005 Sept. 19 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1100)
    - Segment on Dishwashers with Alberto Rojas, Consumer Report, 2005 Mar. 14 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1101)
    - Segment on Inflatable Pool Dangers, 2005 Aug. 04 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1102)
    - Segment with David Heim Re: Bug Repellents, 2003 June 26 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1178)
    - Segment with Janice Lieberman, 2005 Jan. 19 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1103)
    - Shampoo/Saran/Comb Filter, Undated (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0167)
    - Shoes, Toys & Milk, Undated (Box 29, Film-reel RL11802-F16-124)
    - Shopper Segment Tortilla Chips, 1995 Sept. 15 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0184)
    - Short Sheets - Calorie Counter, Undated (Box 18, Film-reel RL11802-F16-087)
    - Smoke Alarms Geoff Martin, 1996 May 17 (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0170)
    - Stain Removers, 2000 Mar. 21 (Box 106a, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1063)
    - Toy Safety - Fuel ADJ, Undated (Box 18, Film-reel RL11802-F16-101)
    - Toy Test 2Lady of Sorrows School, 1998 Nov. 10 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-219)
    - Unsafe Yo-yo Balls, 2003 Oct. 28 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-103)
    - Unsafe yo-yo Balls B-Roll, 2003 Nov. 05 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-293)
    - Winter Survival Gear, 2000 Jan. 29 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1090)
  - Services, 1982-2006; undated; 21
    - Airports, 2000 Sept. 14 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1085)
    - Consumer Reports Best Travel Deals, Undated (Box 85, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0361)
    - Dry Cleaning Coverage, 1995 Oct. 24-25 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0084)
    - Hotel Bargains in New York City, 2001 Jan. 11 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0675)
    - Jeff Fox, Consumer Reports on Spam, 2003 July 09 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1176)
    - Jim Guest & Davi Heim Cell Phones, 2002 Jan. 07 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1223)
    - Joel Gurin- Nursing Homes CBS This Morning, 1995 July 18 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0118)
    - Nursing Home, Undated (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0664)
    - Outlet Malls, Tod Marks, Consumer Reports Nationally Televised Market, 2006 Apr. 11 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1092)
    - The Dollars and Sense Show, 1982 Sept. 22 (Box 37, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-064)
    - Top Ten List Segment on Paris Hilton Buying a Monkey, 2005 Nov. 16 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1105)
  - Testing Policy and Practices, 1941-2008; undated; 22
    - 2005 Auto Test track Testing Demonstration CR Bug (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-205)
    - Auto Tape 3, 2003 Dec. 22 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-242)
    - Auto Track B- Roll Tape 2, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-292)
    - Auto Track B-Roll Tape 1, 2002 Feb. 19 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-291)
    - Car Test Program, 1967 (Box 65, Film-reel RL11802-F8-024)
    - Car Test Program, 1968 (Box 62, Film-reel RL11802-F8-021)
    - Car Test Program, 1968 Aug.; 1968 Sept.; 1968 Oct. (Box 65, Film-reel RL11802-F8-026)
    - Consumer Products Product Tests (microfilm), 1957-1960 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-213)
      Start: Radio sets, speakers project AU20; Ed: Detergents, synthetic, project C130
    - Consumer Products Product Tests (microfilm), 1960-1964 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-214)
      Start: Detergents, synthetic, project C130; End: Cigars, cigarettes vs. small cigars project C238
    - Consumer Products: Ratings, Use in Advertising (microfilm), 1946-1956 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-217)
      Start: Folder 1-3 (weeded 1946-1950); End: Folder 14 (weeded, 1955 Oct.-1956 Apr.)
    - Consumer Products: Ratings, Use in Advertising (microfilm), 1956-1959 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-218)
      Start: Folder 15 (weeded, 1956 May-Dec.); End: Folder 23 (1959 Dec.)
    - Consumer Products: Ratings, Use in Advertising (microfilm), 1960-1961 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-219)
      Start: A-F; End: G-L
    - Consumer Products: Ratings, Use in Advertising (microfilm), 1960-1971 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-221)
      Start: S-Z 1968-1971; End: S-Z 1960-1961
    - Consumer Products: Ratings, Use in Advertising (microfilm), 1962-1964 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-222)
      Start: S-Z 1962-1964; End: Consumers Union Violation of No-Commercialization Policy 1963 Jan.-July
    - Consumer Products: Ratings, Use in Advertising (microfilm), 1962-1971 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-220)
      Start: G-L 1962-1964; End: G-L 1968-1971
    - Consumer Products: Ratings, Use in Advertising (microfilm), 1963-1969 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-223)
      Start: Diapers, disposable 1969 T69; End: Ironing board covers project T100 charts, graphs and scoring 1963
    - Consumer Reports 762.00 (microfilm), 2007 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-012)
      Vol. 72, issues 1-13, Jan.-Dec., including indexes
    - Consumer Reports 762.00 (microfilm), 2008 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-010)
      Vol. 73, issues 7-13, July-Dec., including indexes
    - Consumer Reports 762.00 (microfilm), 2008 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F35-011)
      Vol. 73, issues 1-6, Jan.-June
    - Consumer Reports Auto Issue Demonstrations, 1999-2000 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-255)
    - Consumer Reports Auto Test Track Testing Demonstrations, 1999-2000 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-256)
    - Consumer Reports Auto Test Track Testing Demonstrations, 1999-2000 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-263)
    - Consumer Reports Auto Test Track Testing Demonstrations, 1999-2000 (Box 106, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1017)
    - Consumer Reports Auto Test Track Testing Demonstrations, 1999-2000 (Box 106, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1019)
    - Consumer Reports Auto Test Track Testing Demonstrations, 2000 Mar. 24 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-259)
    - Consumer Reports B-roll-Electronics Labs, 2006 Oct. (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-008)
    - Consumer Reports Chicken Testing Footage, 2001 Jan. (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-005)
    - Consumer Reports Testing, 1997 Sept. 05 (Box 27, Film-reel RL11802-F16-121)
    - Consumer Testing 2 of 4, Undated (Box 34, Film-reel RL11802-F16-133)
    - Consumer Union Short Course Testing at the Transportation Research Center, Undated (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0152)
    - Consumers Union (microfilm), 1941-1947 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-216)
      Start: Photographic Buyers Handbook; End: Bread and Butter vol. 1-7
    - Consumers Union (microfilm), 1961-1962 (Box 138, Film-reel RL11802-F16-215)
      Start: Electronic kits EL26; End: Diapers, disposable T69
    - Foreign Car Test Program, 1967 (Box 29, Film-reel RL11802-F8-012)
    - Foreign Car Testing, 1966 (Box 63, Film-reel RL11802-F8-024)
    - GG Creative Services Consumer Reports Testing W/Phone #, 1997 Sept. 23 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-104)
    - How Consumer Reports Tests Cars (Used on Bus Ride to ATD), 1997 Mar. 13 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0954)
    - How Consumers Union Tests Blankets D, Undated (Box 5, Film-reel RL11802-F35-003)
    - How Consumers Union Tests Blankets L, Undated (Box 5, Film-reel RL11802-F35-001)
    - How Consumers Union Tests Blankets M, Undated (Box 5, Film-reel RL11802-F35-002)
    - How we test @ CU Rico de Paz, Jose Amezequita, and Pat Slaven, 2002 Feb. 12 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1220)
    - How'd They Do That?, Undated (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0085)
    - News 12 Gerard Catapano How we Test Speakers, 2003 Nov. 27 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1210)
    - OPI - SUV Profile on Consumers Union Testing Follow-Up, 2000 June 06 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1078)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0939)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0940)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0944)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0947)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0948)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0949)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0950)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0951)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0952)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0953)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0957)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0958)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0960)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0961)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0965)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0967)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0979)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0980)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0981)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0984)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0985)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0986)
    - Segment on Consumer Testing, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0987)
    - Segments on Consumer Reports Auto test, 2003 Mar. 11 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1189)
    - Senior Director of Auto Testing, 2005 Oct. 30 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1113)
    - Tape 1 Auto Test, 2001 Feb. 16 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-237)
    - Tech Department Program Leader Bob Karpel demonstrating historic test equipment used by CU engineers, 2007 Dec. 07 (Box 58, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-028)
    - Tech Department Program Leader Bob Karpel demonstrating historic test equipment used by CU engineers, 2007 Dec. 07 (Box 58, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-030)
    - Tech Department Program Leader Bob Karpel demonstrating historic test equipment used by CU engineers, 2007 Dec. 07 (Box 58, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-032)
    - Tech seminar: Shoe Testing, 1993 June 24 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0075)
    - The Auto Lab, 2006 Sept. 02 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-350)
    - The Auto Lab Don Mays Consumer Reports, 2005 Apr. 09 (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-243)
    - What's In It, 1994 Nov. 14 (Box 36, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-077)
    - Zillions Rates Products for Kids, 1991 (Box 120, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-219)
    - Zillions Toy test, 1994 Aug. 29 (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0215)
- Public Relations and Publicity, 1961-2011; undated; 6
  - Advocacy, 1973-2006; undated; 23
    - American Consumer NOLA: AMCS, Undated (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1121)
    - APS Presentation Tape Car Safety Show, 1997 Sept. 24 (Box 87, Video-cassette RL11802-DBcam-001)
    - Bose v Consumers Union: US Supreme CT. Arguments, Undated (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-204)
    - Bose vs. Consumers Union, 1994 Nov. 17 (Box 59, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0033)
    - Committee Testimony - Financial Privacy, 2003 Jan. (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0694)
    - Committee Testimony - Financial Privacy, 2003 Jan. (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0695)
    - Consumer Reports National Testing and Research Center, Undated (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-086)
    - Consumer Reports Undercm Avoidance, 1999 Apr. 16 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-136)
    - Consumers Union Drug cartoon, 2006 Mar. 11 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0465)
    - Consumers Union: Clips of Testimony 2001 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0970)
    - Court Room Video Brundage vs Shearburn More Burn Shear-Docs, Undated (Box 137, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-705)
    - Energy Workshop, 1973 Oct. (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-164)
    - E-Ratings Event, 1999 Nov. 09 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0612)
    - ESP Media Training Video, Undated (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0202)
    - Firestone Press Conference, Undated (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1108)
    - Kids and Cars 8 Spots Tied, 2003 Sept. 23 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0795)
    - Litigation, Undated (Box 99, Disk RL11802-FD3-003)
    - Littlest Giant, Undated (Box 2, Film-reel RL11802-F16-014)
    - Nigeria 1962, 1998 Nov. (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0204)
  - Consumers Union Staff, 1961-2011; undated; 24
    - C.E. Warne - Tom Brooks, 1973 Sept. 08 (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-109)
    - C.E. Warne - Tom Brooks, 1973 Sept. 08 (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-110)
    - C.E. Warne - Tom Brooks, 1973 Sept. 08 (Box 76, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-111)
    - C.E. Warne Calhoun College Seminar #181, 1976 Oct. 19 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-070)
    - C.E. Warne History of Consumers Union #182a, 1976 Mar. 31 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-071)
    - C.E. Warne History of Consumers Union #182b, 1976 Mar. 31 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-072)
    - CEW (Colston Warne), 1981 Aug. 22 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-006)
    - Colston Warne Interviewed by Norman Silber #272a, 1980 Aug. 08 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-180)
    - Colston Warne Interviewed by Norman Silber #272b, 1980 Aug. 08 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-181)
    - Colston Warne Interviewed by Norman Silber #273, 1980 Aug. 20 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-182)
    - David Campion/ Gabe Shenher, Undated (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0907)
    - David Champion, 2000 (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0537)
    - David Champion, 2000 June (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1086)
    - David Champion GMA - April Issue Top Picks, 2000 Mar. 16 (Box 106a, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1053)
    - David Pittle, 1998 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0699)
    - David Pittle, 1998 Sept. 28 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-240)
    - David Pittle, 1998 Sept. 28 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-241)
    - David Pittle, 1998 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0146)
    - Dr. Clark Ahlberg Interview; Dean Donald Herzberg Interview both about Persia Campbell #256, 1980 Feb. 27; 1980 Feb. 28 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-164)
    - Dr. Harold Wattel at Hofstra University about Persia Campbell #252, 1980 Jan. 29 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-160)
    - Elizabeth Kultgen Interviewed about Persia Campbell #245, 19-- Oct. 30 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-150)
    - Elizabeth Kultger; Interview with Irma Angevine both about Persia Campbell #267, 1980 Oct. 30; 1981 Jan. 19 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-175)
    - End of RD Pittle Interview w/m Boot Start of RHK interview w/m Boot, Undated (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-242)
    - Farewell Msg to Rhoda H. KKarpatkin From Consumers Union Staffers, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-193)
    - Farewell to Rhoda, 2001 Jan. 26; 2001 Jan. 30 (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-055)
    - Farewell to Rhoda, 2001 Jan. 26; 2001 Jan. 30 (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-MDV-001)
    - Gene Kimmelman & Track Tape 1, 2001 Dec. 06 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-232)
    - Gordon, Leland Chap. 11 - Economics for Consumers, 1975 Mar. (Box 70, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-148)
    - H. Kallen in Class at New School for Social Research #243, 19-- Oct. 09 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-148)
    - Heinlein Farewell, 2005 June (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-119)
    - Herbert Denenberg, Annual Mtg. #184d, 1973 Oct. (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-077)
    - Interview Chaste & Pretle (Pittle?), Undated (Box 78, Video-reel RL11802-vid2-003)
    - Interview of Ed Reich by Sybil Shainwald & Colston Warne #240a, 1980 July 04 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-143)
    - Interview of Ed Reich by Sybil Shainwald & Colston Warne #240b, 1980 July 04 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-144)
    - Interview of Ed Reich by Sybil Shainwald & Colston Warne #240c, 1980 July 04 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-145)
    - Interview of Esther Peterson about Persia Campbell #263, 1980 Oct. 22 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-171)
    - Interview of Helen Harris about Persia Campbell #259, 1980 Mar. 20 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-167)
    - Interview of Meyer Parodneck about Persia Campbell #260, 1980 Aug. 19 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-168)
    - Interview with Colston E. Warne by Peter Samson #209, 1978 Apr. 26 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-135)
    - Interview with Colston Warne #274a, 1983 Aug. 09 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-183)
    - Interview with Colston Warne #274b, 1983 Aug. 09 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-184)
    - Interview with Colston Warne about Persia Campbell #270, 1979 Nov. 02 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-178)
    - Interview with David Champion- Consumer Union/Consumer Reports Spokesperson, 2004 Mar. 09 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0817)
    - Interview with Dr. Aurelia Toya Miller about Persia Campbell #258, 1980 Mar. 12 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-166)
    - Interview with Elizabeth Kultger about Persia Campbell #266, 1980 Oct. 30 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-174)
    - Interview with James Guest, 2003 Sept. 19 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0710)
    - Interview with Joan Faulkner about Persia Campbell #242, 19-- Oct. 04 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-147)
    - Interview with Louis Lefkowitz; Interview with Florence Mason both about Persia Campbell #264, 1980 July 28; 1980 Oct. 27 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-172)
    - Interview with Sidney Rice Katz Nelson about Persia Campbell #265, 1980 Oct. 30 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-173)
    - Interviews with Betty Furness & Helen Nelson about Persia Campbell #261, 1980 Sept. 23 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-169)
    - Interviews with Carol Lubin, Eleanor French, & Carol Jacobson about Persia Campbell #257, 1980 Mar. 13-16 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-165)
    - Interviews with Charles Hoffman, Bill Hamawich and Florence Mason about Persia Campbell #262, 1980 Sept. 25-29 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-170)
    - Interviews with Jonathan Bingham and Al Oxenfeldt about Persia Campbell #255, 1980 Feb. 13-18 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-163)
    - Jean Holloram Richard Cross, 2000 Oct. 02 (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-047)
    - Jean Whitehill, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-027)
    - Jeff Fuerst OPI-Media Training, 2000 Feb. 17 (Box 106a, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1046)
    - Jim Guess Standup, 2002 Dec. 19 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-161)
    - Jim Guest, 2002 Feb. 07 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0689)
    - Jim Guest, 2002 Feb. 07 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0691)
    - Jim Guest, 2008 Jan. 15 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-358)
    - Jim Guest, 2002 Feb. 07 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1222)
    - Jim Guest - Consumers Union President, 2007 June 12 (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-021)
    - Jim Guest - Consumers Union President, 2007 June 12 (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-023)
    - Jim Guest & Patricia Slingo, 2007 June 12 (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-022)
    - Jim Guest Admin Dept. MTG, Undated (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-328)
    - Jim Guest Cell Hell, 2003 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1221)
    - Jim Guest Cell Hell, 2003 Mar. (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0720)
    - Jim Guest Cell hell Reel, 2003 Jan. (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1157)
    - Jim Guest Mario Cuomo #2, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-060)
    - Jim Guest Standups, 02 Dec. 19 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-157)
    - Jim Guest: Healthcare, 2008 Sept. 30 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-349)
    - Joan Claybrook For the Rhoda H. Karpatkin Retrospective, 2000 Oct. (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-043)
    - Joan Claybrook For the Rhoda H. Karpatkin Retrospective, 2000 Oct. (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-045)
    - Joan Claybrook on RHK President-Public Citizen, 2000 Oct. (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-Hi8-001)
    - Joan Gussow on The McCanns #295, 1974 Jan. 15 (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-098)
    - Joel Gurin, 1995 Sept. 19 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0144)
    - Joel Gurin Consumers Union, 2002 Dec. 15 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1166)
    - John Galloway- Consumer Union, Undated (Box 72, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-023)
    - Leonard J. Goldwater Autobiographical #222, 1979 May 07 (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-137)
    - Linda Lipsen & Lea Thompson, 1992 June 24 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0098)
    - Mike Hansen, 1988 Mar. 15 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0106)
    - Mike Pertschuk, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-061)
    - Morris Kaplan Memorial Service #178, 1971 Sept. 19 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-067)
    - Morris Kaplan Memorial Service #179, 1971 Sept. 19 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-068)
    - Morris Kaplan Memorial Service #180, 1971 Sept. 19 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-069)
    - Ned Groth, Undated (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0147)
    - Norman Silber, 2003 June 10 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0028)
    - Persia Campbell Memorial Service #104, 1974 Mar. 23 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-051)
    - Persia Campbell Memorial Service #105, 1974 Mar. 23 (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-052)
    - Ralph Nader #292, 1973 (Box 116, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-095)
    - Ralph Nader Speech at All Eastern Cons. Ed. Conf. #107, 1974 Feb. (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-053)
    - Ralph Nader, Annual Mtg. #184e, 1973 Oct. (Box 113, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-078)
    - Raxane Hofer / PTA David Champion Tape 1, 1999 Apr. 07 (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-246)
    - Raxane Hofer / PTA David Champion Tape 2, 1999 Apr. 07 (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-247)
    - Report on Consumers Union/Gallup Survey on Health Care Reform, 1993 May 28 (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0193)
    - Retirement Party of RHK, 2001 Feb. 15 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0586)
    - RHK Interview Continued/ Ned Groth Interview, Undated (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-236)
    - RHK Retirement Party At Consumers Union, 2001 Feb. 15 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0712)